webmium.com 2015-11-20

# Privacy

At Webmium we care about your privacy and the security of your personal data. We comply applicable with applicable data privacy laws and regulations for your safety and security. In the following we describe what information is collected and how we handle it. This policy applies to all of the Webmium Products. Webmium is a service offered by the Czech company Nexum Trilog a.s. ([www.nexum.cz](http://www.nexum.cz/)).

If you have any questions about this Policy, please don't hesitate to [contact us](mailto:privacy@webmium.com) or write to Webmium Project, ATTN:  **nexum Trilog a.s.,  ** Kolbenova 942/38a,  190 00 Praha 9, Czech Republic.

Webmium collects, processes, and uses personal data of a user without further necessary agreement only insofar as it is necessary for the establishment, fulfillment, and billing of the contract.

Webmium is a website building and hosting service provided at [www.webmium.com](http://www.webmium.com/) and its directly associated domains, tools, services and applications that are operated by Nexum Trilog a.s. (collectively, "Webmium" or "Services").

This "Privacy Policy" explains what information we gather from our users and how we use it. By using or accessing our Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. (Capitalized terms not defined herein have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service).

Webmium is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we will never knowingly gather or use personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, and we do not allow anyone under the age of 13 to register on Webmium.

## What information does Webmium gather?

Webmium gathers and stores three types of information about users that are subject to our Privacy Policy:

### Information users provide to us:

These are voluntary submissions made when creating an account on Webmium or through your use of the Services, such as your name, date of birth, location and email address provided during registration, Content posted, or payment information provided during purchases. Please understand that when you sign into Webmium or post Content, your information is not anonymous to us.

### Information we collect when you interact with Webmium:

We keep track of the actions you take on Webmium, such as adding an application, or posting Content. Also, when you access our Services, we may collect information about your access method (such as hardware and software attributes), location, IP address, and pages you visit. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies". (For more on cookies, please see the section What are cookies?)

### Information we receive from third parties:

We do not own or operate the third-party applications, user Webmium websites and other services offered that you may use or interact with through Webmium (collectively, "Webmium-enhanced" applications, Webmium websites and services). Whenever you visit, use or interact with a Webmium -enhanced application, Webmium website or service, we will receive information from them, including information about actions you take and Content you post on that application, Webmium website or service.

## Why does Webmium gather information about me?

Webmium collects information in order to provide a safe, efficient and customized experience. This information allows us to better tailor our content to users' needs and to help us better understand the demographics of our audience. Webmium may use some of this information for contacting you, customizing the content and advertising you view, improving our services, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting for clients. We only collect personally identifiable information from you because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to enjoy certain Services.

## How will Webmium websites and Applications on Webmium treat my information?

As mentioned above, we do not own or operate Webmium-enhanced applications, Webmium websites and services. We take steps to ensure that providers of Webmium -enhanced applications, Webmium websites and services use information that you share on Webmium in a manner consistent with your privacy settings and the terms of this Privacy Policy, but we cannot guarantee that they will follow our rules. Please take the time to familiarize yourself with the privacy settings of your account, as well as the settings and policies of the applications, Webmium sites and services that you visit, add or use on Webmium. Here are some specific things to remember:

By visiting or becoming a Member of a Webmium site on Webmium , the Content and information you provide during the registration process (including your email address) and other interactions with the Webmium website may be accessed by the Webmium site Creator and their authorized representatives and administrators, as well as any Application Developer whose Applications run on that Webmium website.

By adding or using an Application or a service provided by one of our affiliates or business partners, the information you provide in the interactions with that Application or service may be accessed by the respective Application Developer, affiliate or business partner and their authorized representatives.

When you post information on a Webmium website, that information is subject to that Webmium website's privacy settings and privacy policy, which may change from time to time.

Publicly available information may be accessed by everyone on the Internet, including third-party search engines that may index, cache and store that information.

You should always review the policies of third party Webmium websites, applications and services to make sure you are comfortable with the ways in which they use information you share with them. Any information you share with them is at your own risk. If you find an application, Webmium website or service that violates our rules, you should report the violation to us, and we reserve the right to take action as we deem appropriate without assuming any obligation or liability to do so.

## What are cookies?

Webmium may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. These cookies help us make Webmium easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and Webmium. For example, a cookie may be used to store or "remember" your Member login information (but not your password) so that you are not required to manually log into the site at every visit. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use some of our Services.

Our advertisers and partners may also set cookies through our Services. For more information, please see the section "What about third party advertisers and links?"

## Google Analytics

Webmium.com uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## What about third party advertisers and links?

In the course of serving advertisements on Webmium, a third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Additionally, some links from Webmium may lead to Webmium websites operated by other companies. While these Webmium websites and advertisements may be co-branded with our name or logo, they are not operated or maintained by us. We do not control these cookies and users of Webmium Services should check the privacy policy of the relevant advertiser to understand whether and how it uses cookies. Webmium is not responsible for Webmium websites operated by third parties that are linked to by any of our sites. Ads appearing on this Webmium website, Webmium, and sites hosted by Webmium may be delivered to you by Google Ad Manager, DoubleClick, or other advertising partners. Information about your visits to this site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you.

## How secure is my information?

Webmium uses commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. We limit access to personal information about you to employees whom we believe reasonably need that information to provide support, products, or services to you or to fulfill their roles within our organization.

Although we have established and maintain security procedures to protect your personally identifiable information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share on Webmium will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures on Webmium. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up-to-date antivirus software.

Please [report](mailto:privacy@webmium.com) any security violations to us.

## How private is the Content I upload?

Any Content uploaded or created using our Services and posted on a Webmium website are by default hosted for the public and are thus publicly accessible.

Please note that even if you do not publish links to Content or submit links to a search engine, individuals or search engines may discover and link to your Content by data-mining, guessing the address, spidering sites, or other methods.

## What control do I have over my information?

As a registered member, you may modify or update your personal account information at any time by logging into your account and (a) accessing the Settings area for each Webmium website you have created, and (b) accessing the Manage Profile area for each Webmium website you have joined by clicking on the corresponding Edit Profile link on your Dashboard page. You may also remove the Webmium website(s) you may have created on Webmium at any time by logging into your account and clicking on the corresponding "Delete Site" link on your Dashboard page. Should you desire to do so, you may also delete and close your Webmium account at any time by [contacting](mailto:webmium@webmium.com) us. Note that removed or deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time.

## How is information shared?

Webmium will not share your personally identifiable information with others except as described herein with regards to sharing with Webmium -enhanced applications, Webmium websites and services and in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the Services, legally required, or permitted by you. For example, we may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the Services at a co-location facility for servers, to register your domain name, to send out email updates about Webmium, to provide you with email functionality for your domain, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time.

Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Webmium-specified purposes. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Webmium (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Webmium , whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Webmium Terms of Service or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety or rights of members of the public or users of the Services. Webmium reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Webmium or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

## How am I notified of changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy pursuant to the procedures outlined in our Terms of Service. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you by publication here.

## Changes to this policy

This Privacy Policy may change. Of course, we will not reduce your rights without your explicit consent. All of the Policy changes will be posted on this page. If the changes are significant we will provide a more significant notice (i.e. email notification). If you don't agree with the changes of our privacy statement, it is possible to beg to differ within one month. After this period of time, the changes are considered to be accepted. Please enter your objection via [E-Mail](mailto:privacy@webmium.com) or write to Webmium Project, ATTN:  **nexum Trilog a.s.,  ** Kolbenova 942/38a,  190 00 Praha 9, Czech Republic.
